<?xml version="1.0"?>
<root>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20150065581</patent_id>
    <inventor>Lederman; Seth; et al.</inventor>
    <report_date>March 5, 2015</report_date>
    <title>METHODS AND COMPOSITIONS FOR TREATING FATIGUE ASSOCIATED WITH DISORDERED SLEEP USING VERY LOW DOSE CYCLOBENZAPRINE</title>
    <abstract>The present invention relates to methods for the treatment or prevention of fatigue associated with disordered sleep, for example, in multiple sclerosis, fibromyalgia, Fabry's disease, Parkinson's disease, or traumatic brain injury, using cyclobenzaprine. The present invention further relates to a biomarker for the therapeutic effects of a cyclobenzaprine treatment.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=1&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20140336264</patent_id>
    <inventor>Nebuloni; Marino; et al.</inventor>
    <report_date>November 13, 2014</report_date>
    <title>EUTECTIC FORMULATIONS OF CYCLOBENZAPRINE HYDROCHLORIDE AND AMITRIPTYLINE HYDROCHLORIDE</title>
    <abstract>The present invention relates to pharmaceutical compositions and methods of manufacturing the same, comprising a eutectic of Cyclobenzaprine HCl and mannitol or Amitriptyline HCl and mannitol.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=2&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20140212486</patent_id>
    <inventor>LEDERMAN; SETH; et al.</inventor>
    <report_date>July 31, 2014</report_date>
    <title>ISOMETHEPTENE ISOMER</title>
    <abstract>The invention relates to a purified Isometheptene compound comprising the structure according to Formula (I), ##STR00001## or a hydrochloride, or a pharmaceutically acceptable addition salt thereof. In particular, the disclosure relates to the synthesis, purification and characterization of an Isometheptene isomer mucate crystal 2, wherein the Isometheptene isomer 2 is stereochemically characterized as (R)-enantiomer, respectively. The Isometheptene (R)-enantiomer activity indicates a selective centrally acting selective ligand for Imidazoline subtype 1 (I1) receptor sites; and more specifically, the disclosure provides an antihypertensive composition for treatment of migraine and other neurovascular or neurogenic pain from abdominal distress. (R)-Isometheptene enantiomer or isomer 2 may be an anti-hypertensive agent with lower side effects than the racemate form. Therefore (R)-Isometheptene is believed to be effective against episodic tension-type headaches (ETTH). The (R)-Isometheptene enantiomer or isomer 2 is believed to effectively lower blood pressure, used alone or together with other headache ameliorating drugs. Methods of synthesis and treatment are described. Regarding (R)-Isometheptene crystals data of X-ray crystallography are presented.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=3&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20140171515</patent_id>
    <inventor>Lederman; Seth; et al.</inventor>
    <report_date>June 19, 2014</report_date>
    <title>COMPOSITIONS AND METHODS FOR TRANSMUCOSAL ABSORPTION</title>
    <abstract>The invention provides compositions and methods for administering compounds for transmucosal absorption. The compositions and methods have a number of surprising pharmacokinetic benefits over oral administration of a compound.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=4&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20130165511</patent_id>
    <inventor>Lederman; Seth; et al.</inventor>
    <report_date>June 27, 2013</report_date>
    <title>TREATMENT FOR COCAINE ADDICTION</title>
    <abstract>A novel pharmaceutical composition is provided for the control of stimulant effects, in particular treatment of cocaine addiction, or further to treatment of both cocaine and alcohol dependency, including simultaneous therapeutic dose application or a single dose of a combined therapeutically effective composition of disulfiram and selegiline compounds or pharmaceutically acceptable non-toxic salt thereof.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=5&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20120232159</patent_id>
    <inventor>Lederman; Seth</inventor>
    <report_date>September 13, 2012</report_date>
    <title>Methods and Compositions for Treating Depression using Cyclobenzaprine</title>
    <abstract>The present invention relates to methods for the treatment or prevention of depression, and related pharmaceutical compositions. Of particular interest are pharmaceutical compositions comprising cyclobenzaprine, alone, or in combination with an antidepressant drug.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=6&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20120101154</patent_id>
    <inventor>Lederman; Seth</inventor>
    <report_date>April 26, 2012</report_date>
    <title>COMPOSITIONS AND METHODS FOR INCREASING COMPLIANCE WITH THERAPIES USING ALDEHYDE DEHYDROGENASE INHIBITORS AND TREATING ALCOHOLISM</title>
    <abstract>Compositions and methods for treating, preventing, or reducing alcoholism, in particular methods for increasing patient compliance with therapies that require the intake of an ALDH inhibitor comprising the step of administering a monoamine oxidase B inhibitor.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=7&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20110319389</patent_id>
    <inventor>Lederman; Seth; et al.</inventor>
    <report_date>December 29, 2011</report_date>
    <title>METHODS AND COMPOSITIONS FOR TREATING FATIGUE ASSOCIATED WITH DISORDERED SLEEP USING VERY LOW DOSE CYCLOBENZAPRINE</title>
    <abstract>The present invention relates to methods for the treatment or prevention of fatigue associated with disordered sleep, for example, in multiple sclerosis, fibromyalgia, Fabry's disease, Parkinson's disease, or traumatic brain injury, using cyclobenzaprine The present invention further relates to a biomarker for the therapeutic effects of a cyclobenzaprine treatment.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=8&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
  <patent>
    <patent_id>20110124656</patent_id>
    <inventor>Seth; Lederman; et al.</inventor>
    <report_date>May 26, 2011</report_date>
    <title>Methods and Compositions for Treating Symptoms Associated with Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder using Cyclobenzaprine</title>
    <abstract>The present invention relates to methods for the treatment or prevention of symptoms associated with post-traumatic stress disorder, and related pharmaceutical compositions. Of particular interest are pharmaceutical compositions comprising a very low dose of cyclobenzaprine, alone, or in combination with an alpha-1-adrenergic receptor antagonist, a beta-adrenergic antagonist, an anticonvulsant, a selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor or a serotonin-norepinephrine reuptake inhibitor.</abstract>
    <link>http://appft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO2&amp;Sect2=HITOFF&amp;p=1&amp;u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsearch-bool.html&amp;r=9&amp;f=G&amp;l=50&amp;co1=OR&amp;d=PG01&amp;s1=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AS.&amp;s2=%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22.AANM.&amp;OS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22&amp;RS=AN/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22+OR+AANM/%22Tonix+Pharmaceuticals%22</link>
  </patent>
</root>
